I've brought it to the top of my list, by any chance.
What do you mean, you brought it?
It's so cute.
It's the cutest thing I've ever seen from the side.
Hello everyone, I'm Rei Oizono of Sakana Zakao 46.
I'm in a hotel in the Philippines.
I would like to crash into the members' rooms here and check their personal belongings.
I'm off. It's like a sleep-wake-up surprise.
Good morning. I am now going to the sleeping quarters of our members.
I'm going to go raid the members' sleeping quarters. Secret check.
Okay, first of all, we've arrived in front of the first room. Let's press the button.
They're probably afraid of the cutting-edge ding-dong.
It's glowing.
Who's that?
Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
I'm in Suzuki's room.
Good morning
Good morning.
Let's see them one at a time.
Suzuki's not really good at this.
Did I say it out loud?
I'm not good at it.
Try to come and buy it.
I bought this...
I bought this neck pillow.
It's so good.
It stabilized me so much.
I bought it.
I think it's important to have a neck pillow.
When the other seniors are around
They're so cute.
I'm not sure I'm good with cute.
I don't know if I'm a sucker for cute things.
You're right. I'm not there yet.
I'm still a beginner.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
I'll use it.
Next time.
Wherever you go.
I'd like to bring it with me wherever I go.
It's a stool.
It's cute.
This one's called a dormouse.
A dormouse?
There's an animal.
The animal's name is...
A dormouse?
Like a cat.
A dormouse.
Cute.
Cute dormouse!
This is Hanamaru.
So cute!
I picked these two.
I picked them out.
I'm not going to put them on.
I'm going to put them on.
We're moving together.
We're both...
We'll have rings to put on.
We're gonna put it on.
Next.
Security buzzer
Cute
I bought this one with a cat buzzer.
I bought this one.
I'm going abroad.
Did you use it?
No, I haven't.
You have to use it.
It's a safe trip.
I'm sure you'll be doing a lot of traveling.
We'll be moving around a lot.
We'll be moving around a lot, so we'll need to be able to protect ourselves.
You're pushing it?
This one.
Pull it.
This way, the light will come on.
You always light the way at night, don't you?
I can join in.
It's so nice!
This is also a security buzzer.
Very important!
It's so cute!
I don't always let them draw this.
I don't let him paint it, but...
It's a make-up stage.
It might be small.
Only the best of the best.
That's for sure.
I didn't bring any eye shadow.
I'll have a makeup artist do it.
I only put in the makeup for the parts I'm particular about.
I only put makeup on the parts I'm particular about.
I bought this overseas.
I also bought this.
A phone?
It's for hanging around your neck.
You can use it to wear it around your neck.
It's cute.
It's sparkly.
I like pink.
I'm pretty sure I have an image of it.
The security buzzer is pink, too.
This is so cute!
I bought it because I fell in love with it at first sight.
It's so convenient to wear it around your neck, isn't it?
It's so convenient!
You can take a picture right away.
Security.
It's very secure.
Stylish security.
I use it on airplanes.
Tamagotchi
I miss it.
It's good, isn't it?
It's been a while since I played Tamagotchi.
It's so much fun.
Is it alive? Alive?
Sick.
It's beeping.
Does it call to you?
Is it calling for me to shush?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
How do you lose weight?
The Tamagotchi now has a button.
It's a slide.
Does it have touch?
It's a treatment.
Treatment?
I want to be cured.
Great.
Last one.
The last one.
I had it in my suitcase.
Suitcase.
It's the first time I'm going abroad
I thought I would miss Japanese food.
I thought I'd bring my
Japanese food I've brought with me.
As one would expect.
The list
Cup Ramen.
You really love it!
The last Japanese meal...
We came to the list for dinner.
You said you had already decided when you were rehearsing.
That's right.
We decided after rehearsal that we would definitely go to the list afterwards.
With that mindset
I did my best.
Bring this.
This is for the fun on the last day.
I see.
If you have hot water, you can eat it.
That's right.
Cup noodles.
What a gap!
Pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink.
I feel like I want one.
Your belongings are overflowing.
Thank you
It's like this.
Thank you for introducing me.
The next member of the group.
We're here in front of the next member's room.
Ding-dong.
Good morning. Good morning.
This is my villa.
A villa?
Yes, it is.
I'm going to go to Ding-dong's room.
Excuse me.
Not at all. Please, sit down.
Oh, wow.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's take a look at Tila's
I'd like to show you some of Tila's personal belongings
I'd like to take a look at your personal belongings that you brought overseas.
Well, when I go abroad, I'll definitely bring some of my personal belongings.
What's that?
That's amazing!
I'm famous for having a pointy butt.
It hurts so much when I sit for a long time.
That's great.
So that's what that is.
I get on airplanes all the time.
I do it all the time.
You look so happy and puffy.
It's like a cushion for your butt.
It's like a cushion.
When Ray and I went to Australia together.
I had a really bad butt when I went to Australia with Ray and me.
I learned a lot in Australia.
I learned a lot.
I'm going to get another one of these
everyone's favorite neck pillow.
I guess everyone has one.
I absolutely love the hooded one.
I love it.
It's so cute.
This is how I like to lie down
hooded
Nyan Cat
It's so cute.
And it gives me a really nice face.
And it protects her neck.
It's so cute.
Look at this.
Look at that.
When he lays his legs down...
That's why...
That's why this is an airplane.
That's great
Put the string on the desk.
And hang it up.
So you can put it right there.
That's easy.
I forgot the string.
He was so happy yesterday.
You can use it.
I even tried to do it with my hands.
I tried to do it with my hands, but it was too hard.
I can use this one.
When you go abroad
You make a checklist, right?
I'll make sure to check it.
Check it off.
Get in the car.
I thought it was perfect, but it wasn't.
I wanted it to be more like this.
You're supposed to hook it and catch your foot on it.
So I had to put it on one side of the desk.
I was only lifting one leg.
Okay, Kira, let's see what you've got.
Kira-chan's airplane goods!
Kira, the airplane pro.
I'm Kira.
I assisted her.
It's Kira!
This is Kira flying.
I'd like to go in for the third one.
Come on.
Is he awake? Oh, yeah, I think they're awake.
Oh!
Ta-da! Good morning, Yuzu!
Good morning, Mr. Ray.
I'm here, I'm forced to enter.
Your hair looks so cute today.
Thank you, it's my first time.
It's so cute! Rei!
Excuse me.
Hello. Come on in.
I'd like to show you some of my personal items that I brought overseas.
I'd like to see some of them.
May I introduce them to you?
Please introduce me.
I'll bring them.
Thank you.
What? What do you mean, you brought it?
It's huge.
Can I bring this to everyone?
I didn't bring it.
Put it in the carry-on.
Water.
I was nervous about it, so I brought it, but I haven't drank it yet.
I haven't drank it yet, but you're right.
But they say the water here is really good.
It really is like Japanese water.
Really? Is it?
Yes, it's good.
When Yu Murai brushed his teeth...
He used bottled water, right?
Here?
I don't know about the tap, but it's in the fridge or something.
It's in the fridge or something?
You haven't seen it, have you?
I didn't see it.
It's water.
That's good.
Where's the other one?
One more.
Ta-da!
It's so cute.
What's this?
It's a kitten.
Nyakki?
You know what I mean.
It's a snake towel, like clay.
It's Nyakki's towel.
It's so cute!
I wanted to carry it with me, so I slept like this.
Are you sleeping with a Nyakki cap on your head? I'm going to give it to Nyakki.
Thank you very much for the water and the water for the ear.
Here is the last one
Wow, Shinzan mom is so cool!
Could it be that this one is used and this one is used too?
You're the type of person who can hold your own shoes
You're wearing you's!
Yay!
So cute!
Reina, the third generation...
Reina Sakura put this on herself for fun.
I like her make-up pouch.
I haven't seen many people wearing their own kanpachi on their make-up pouches
I've never seen so many people wearing their own kanpachi on their makeup bag.
Is that why she left it behind?
If you leave something behind, the manager will give it to you.
Like a name.
Like your name.
The other day, he wrote it like a name.
A nameplate.
I'm using it as a new name tag.
That's a handy recommendation.
I think it's useful.
Let's do it.
Let's do it together!
It's a little embarrassing.
It's so cute.
We're all in! We're all in!
Maybe it's a good idea. It's easy to understand.
It's kind of used, isn't it?
Yes, this three-piece set.
You're so cute!
Yay!
It really brings out the individuality, doesn't it?
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
See you later.
We left together.
Congratulations on being the polite type.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Good night.
Good morning
Good morning.
You must be Hicca.
Well, I'm going to go crash in your room.
Thank you.
I'd like to show you some of my personal belongings that I brought with me to the Philippines.
I'd like to show you some of them.
Sure.
Okay.
Hiccup-ish things.
The first one is...
Ta-da!
Wow!
Kabigon.
I'm sure you may recognize this one.
Yes, I have it.
Yes, I do.
Do you think you might have gone to the Scrad Slope Channel to buy it?
I went to the Pokemon Center to buy it.
Correct!
I'm using Kabigon.
The back is
The back is the same, so it's a 3-way
That's right.
When you open it, you can see the chukka.
Kabigon
Cute!
And...
Kabigon.
That's what I saw when I was on the move.
That's it... that's what I saw.
I've seen this, I've seen this.
The move was kind of cute.
It's a face-type thing.
I was chasing him around, chasing him around, chasing him around.
And then...
I know what you mean.
Mini Cute
Compression
I'm wearing
To the knee.
It's all about length, isn't it?
It comes out.
There's so many different kinds.
There's the bottom.
Or the kind that go in like pants.
Below the knee, too.
And not the cool kind.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's nice.
Let's continue.
Oh!
What's this?
It's a foot roll.
You know, we use these during rehearsal.
Have you seen it?
Yes, I have.
Oh, my God, I'm slipping.
You can tell it's Nikko's table when you see it.
She carries it around with her in Japan, too.
You sure love it.
I carry it with me on dance days.
To relax?
To relax my feet.
Heh.
You can use it anywhere. Even your arms.
Does the board feel good?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, this...
The relax series?
This is for the head.
I use this a lot.
A lot of people use it.
This one has a little bit of firmness to it.
Is this the middle one?
Soft, normal.
It's normal.
It's in the middle. It's just right.
This really makes a difference.
You need to loosen up the scalp.
You know, if you've been on a plane or something long enough.
It's a little ticklish.
So just loosen it up.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Weak, weak, weak.
That's good.
Let me see.
What's this?
What's that?
It's a foot sheet.
They're really good.
You put them on the soles?
It's like... Heavy Liquid Powder.
Heavy liquid powder.
Did you make this?
This is...
It's a heavy powder and a sheet.
You put a sheet like a scene on it.
You put it on your feet and go to sleep.
Sleep with it. Sleep with it.
When you wake up in the morning.
You wake up in the morning, you'll be black like this.
It absorbs it.
It's like Rawhives.
It'll make your legs feel lighter.
Wow, I'm really into this.
Let's try it.
It's totally different.
I'll definitely bring it.
I'll bring the tour and everything.
Oh, yeah.
I love it. I love it.
Have you been drinking a lot?
We're my fans. We're always drinking.
No, we don't.
You like the taste?
I've been drinking it since I was, like, five years old.
I've been drinking it since I was about five.
You've been drinking it since you were five?
I drink a lot.
Calorie Mate Jelly, apple flavor.
Apple is good.
I got about eight of them.
He drank a lot.
Don't worry about it.
Favorite thing in Japan?
Food and drink.
It makes you feel safe.
I'm just not used to it.
I've got this.
Don't worry about it.
It's important, it's important.
I'll be back next time.
Last one.
This is overseas.
Overseas.
Phone strap
Could this be...
New World
there and there
I have one.
It's nice and soft, isn't it?
It doesn't bite.
It's also good for security.
You'll love it.
We're going to walk now.
Let's use it.
I'm off.
Thank you for introducing me to so many people.
Thank you very much.
Have a good night.
Bye-bye.
This is the last member of our room raid.
That's all for now.
Wow, Mr. Yui!
Excuse me.
We're going to raid your rooms!
Today, we'll be looking at the personal belongings that the members have brought overseas.
Personal effects?
I'm going to ask them to show us their personal belongings.
I wonder...
Oh, there's something here.
Well, then, please go ahead.
Please do.
What?
Wow.
Ajama.
Wow, maybe.
So cute!
I got these from Fuu-chan.
A cat?
Yes, a cat.
So cute!
Fluffy.
I wonder if this is the family next door.
That's nice.
Looks calm.
And Mako-chan.
Oh...
I've seen Kira's before.
The one from Pampa that Mako gave me.
You know, the one...
The cat-shaped pouch...
It had a large capacity.
I'm sure.
I put my skin care products in it.
It's the perfect size and lightweight.
It's lightweight and cute.
It's so cute when you look at it from the side.
Tap-tap-tap.
It's so cute.
It's skin care.
That's nice.
This one, Airplane.
I've had this one for a long time.
I've been bringing him with me.
This is her.
Yeah, it's a blanket, but...
I see.
It's cold on airplanes and stuff.
I was next door, wasn't I?
Yes.
No, no, no, no.
Next door?
He's good here, isn't he?
He has a nice mouth.
He's cute.
Like this.
A lot of different creatures, a lot of different possessions.
So many creatures, so cute!
Is that a book?
Is it a book this time?
What?
It's an event hosted by Magi Artist Word in Korea.
It's a Korean event.
A little Korean.
I'm sure the staff speaks a lot of Korean.
I thought there would be a lot of Korean.
Wow!
I don't know much about it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so happy.
We rehearsed all in Korean.
I don't know...
It was amazing.
It was my first experience with English.
Somehow.
Yes.
I felt like I was saying yes.
Thank you so much for introducing us!
You are so cute!
Thank you very much.
The last one was Yui.
Yes, that's right.
Five members introduced their personal belongings to us.
of the precious members.
I think it was a precious belongings of the members
I think they are precious belongings of the members.
I hope you all will take these items with you when you go abroad.
When you are going out or going abroad
When you go abroad, please refer to this video.
If you like this video
Subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
I was just saying an important line.
I'll ask you to say it with me.
Okay. - Okay.
What do you say?
Subscribe to our channel.
Give us a rating.
I'd love to hear your comments.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Subscribe to our channel
Highly Recommended
Comment
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Lots of stuff!
Please, please, please, please.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm excited to be going overseas.
Bye-bye.